totallyphp.co.uk 2006-06-18

# Privacy Statement - Totally PHP

[Home](http://www.totallyphp.co.uk/) > **Privacy Statement**

Last Updated: 8th February 2004.

Totally PHP is committed to maintaining the trust of our users. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect information from you, and what we do with that information.

## The Information We Collect

We may collect and store information such as IP address, the pages you visit, and basic computer information such as resolution and browser. This information is used in order to monitor site traffic and statistics.

Should you register on this website in order to use forums, receive newsletters etc, then we will request your name, email address and other basic information. Should we pass any of this information on to third parties, we will never disclose your name or other personally identifiable information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a text file containing information that is placed on your computer by a website. We may use cookies in order to identify which pages our users visit and to store information to remember that a user is logged in to our website. We may also use cookies for advertising purposes, and these cookies may come from third parties such as advertising networks, to which we may not have access. We do not store information in a cookie regarding anything other than your visit to this website.

## Disclosure of Information

We may use any information collected for our own usage, and we may pass this information to third parties in order to target content or advertisements, or to enhance your experience at this website. In the event that any information collected by us is demanded from us by a court of law, we will make this information accessible to them. There may also be occasions when we experience technical problems, or when unauthorised persons gain access to information collected by ourselves, and we cannot guarantee the security of the information.

## Changes To This Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy at any time, and the latest version will always be available at this web page.

## Questions

Should you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy you may contact us by email at privacy@totallyphp.co.uk.
